That is, I understand correctly that in
То есть я правильно понимаю что в 14м
1414 Ukraine wanted there to
году Украина захотела чтобы на Донбассе
be no Russian passports in the Donbass. Yes, Russian passports
не было русских паспортов Да русских
and Russian schools. Well, look at the schools, but there
а русских школ Ну школ так смотри а на
were no Russian passports in the Donbass;
Донбассе и не было русских паспортов там
it was Ukraine, then there were Ukrainian
это же Украина была то там украинские
passports there, why? Well, I’m from Donbass  this was
паспорта почему Ну я с Донбасса это была
the territory of Ukraine How could there be
территория Украины Как там могли быть
Russian
русские
passports there Hello, you are from Ukraine Yes, you are,
паспорта Здравствуйте вы с Украины Да вы
I see your
я вижу ваш
lag You are from Russia From what
лаг Вы из России Из какого
city did you come to Moscow from Moscow
города из Москвы приехали в Москву
From where does it matter? I
откуда А какая разница
wonder what city you are from,
Интересно а вы с какого
the city of
города город
Khmelnitsky Please tell me how
Хмельницкий Скажите пожалуйста как у вас
the situation is there?  they are bombing us
обстановка бомбят нас
How do you feel about the fact that Russia is
Как как вы относитесь к тому что Россия
bombing
бомбит
Ukraine? In general, in principle, we have a negative attitude towards the
Украину мы относимся вообще в принципе к
war; we don’t like it all.
войне отрицательно нам это всё не
We want the
нравится Мы хотим уже быстрее чтобы
sanctions to end quickly; the
прекратились санкции прекратилась
war to end; what? What are you doing to
война что Что вы делаете чтобы
stop the war and stop the
прекратилась война и прекратились
sanctions;  the century is in the
санкции А что мы можем сделать XX век на
yard I thought the war was generally far away The
дворе Я думала война - это вообще далеко
collective farm system this whole thing this is
Колхозная система вся вот это дено это
all over a long time ago this Well, it’s
всё давно давно закончилось это Ну как
just that I don’t communicate with anyone from Russia
Просто я вот с кем из России не общаюсь
everyone is against the war everyone wants it to end no
все против войны все хотят её окончания
one is doing anything What will we do
никто ничего не делаем А что мы сделаем
I don’t  I know, I don’t live in Russia, I don’t
Я не знаю я же не живу в России я не
know what’s possible with Well, we are not Putin’s
знаю что можно с Ну так мы же не Путина
children. We are not his family, not relatives,
дети Мы же не его семья не родственники
what should we do? Whose Crimea do you think
что мы делать должны А как считаете чей
Crimea is, I know that it is located on
Крым я знаю что это находится на
the territory of Ukraine, but it belongs to
территории Украины но он принадлежит
this Russia
этому России
What does it mean How to understand it is on the
Что значит Как это понять находится на
territory of Ukraine and Ukrainian belongs to Russia
территории Украины а принадлежит России
And why does it belong to
украинский А почему он принадлежит
Russia Well, I don’t know because
России Ну не знаю потому что наверно
Putin probably took Crimea in 2014 Well,
Путин отобрал Крым в 2014 году Ну а ты
what kind of country do you think Crimea should
как считаешь Крым какой страной должен
be? Well, of course, if it’s
быть Ну понятное дело если он находится
in Ukraine it should be  Ukraine, but it was
на Украине должен быть Украины но это же
n’t me who beat it off correctly. I can’t
не я отбила правильно Я же не могу
say. Give it back.
сказать Подарите назад его
Look, you
Смотри
can, why can’t you
это можешь почему не можешь ты умеешь
speak? I gave you the gift of speech. Yeah, and
разговаривать дал тебе дар речи Ага и
Putin is like that. Well, of course, they told me to
Путин такой Ну конечно мне сказали
give it back. And I’m like that, now someone
отдать И я такой сейчас кто-то там
said it, and I’m like that.  Now, well, if there are
сказал и я такой Сейчас ну если вот
more people like you Yes, because
таких как ты будет больше Да потому что
everyone is silent and says What am I and what am I and
все молчат и говорят А что я а что я а
what am I Well, because we want peace, we
что я Ну так потому что мы хотим мира мы
don’t even want to get involved in this at all, this is
не хотим вообще в это даже ввязываться
why they will come to us All of us are who we are
нам это зачем нас придут Всё мы кто мы
nobody  the
никто
people who you work for are ordinary
люди кем работаете обычные
people I'm in a bank
люди Я в банке
Work as now sanctions have affected the
Работа как сейчас санкции повлияли на
banking system
банковскую систему
Of course I heard Nabiulina
Конечно я слышал набиулина
raised the rate to 21% of
подняла ставку до 21%
Russia Well of course it's a pity we're not tyrants
России Ну конечно жалко мы же не тираны
we're nerd and we feel sorry for our own of course we all
мы же нер и своих жалко конечно все
feel sorry for our own whom you feel sorry for some of the
жалко своих кого вам Жалко ну некоторых
boys  we were mobilized for nothing, that is, not
пацанов у нас же мобили Зро то есть не
on their own. Well, if not on their own. Well, they
по своей же во Ну как не по своей Ну они
went of their own free will. Well, if they hadn’t
пошли по своей воле А ну если бы они не
gone and I don’t know, they would have been put in prison.
пошли и их бы я не знаю в тюрьму
That’s if they were put in
посадили Вот это если бы их посадили в
prison. It’s not of their own free will.  they were imprisoned according to their will
тюрьму Это не по своей воле их посадили
And they went on their own, they signed then according to
А пошли на сво они подписали тогда по
their own And what should they do? Look, well,
своей А что им делать Вот смотри хорошо
here’s an interesting question: if a person Yes, the
вот интересный вопрос если человеку Да
authorities will come to him tomorrow, says
придёт завтра к нему власти говорит
Look, you owe a little girl, Otherwise,
Смотри ты должен маленькую девочку Иначе
we’ll put you in prison and what about the girl,
мы тебя посадим в тюрьму и что девоч
well, if the person then  he will shoot Well, just like that,
го ну если человек то он застрелит Ну
he went to his all, he went to
так же и на сво всё он пошл пошл на
his own Yes, why is it the other way around
сво Да почему наоборот
and he gets the money? Yes, they
и деньги получает получает
will. Well, the mobile phones that are called
он Да получатся Ну мобили званные
get the money,
получают деньги
yes, that is, look, if the person Yes, that’s
да то есть смотри если человеку Да вот
real Yes, he will say, look, either you’re a
реально Да скажет смотри либо ты сейчас
girl now, or we’ll put you in  prison,
девочку Либо мы тебя посадим в тюрьму
here the tyrant Putin says and dude, he doesn’t
вот тиран Путин говорит и чувак он не
go to prison, the girl takes him and then
садится в тюрьму берёт девочка так и тут
he gets it, they tell him either you go to
он получается ему говорят или идёшь
people in Ukraine or to prison, okay, I’m going to
людей в Украине или в тюрьму хорошо иду
people, look, the situation is so correct, you
людей смотри ситуация такая правильно
Don, yes, you have him for 8 years, yes, here he is
Дон да у вас вы его 8 лет вот да вот его
just  poor girls, women, children were spinning
просто бедные девушки женщины дети пряли
I mean, I mean, so Donbass is the other way around
В смысле В смысле так Донбасс наоборот
Russia Donbass is Ukraine and Russia has
Россия Донбасс - это Украина да Россия с
been shelling Donbass since 1914
четырнадцатого года обстреливает Донбасс
why is Russia Putin, on the contrary, has now
почему россия-то Путин наоборот сейчас
finished drinking the war Russia attacked in
допился война Россия напала в
144, not in any year Russia
четырнадцатом году не в чем году Россия
attacked
напала на
Donbass as far as I know  that for 8 years you have been
Донбас насколько я знаю то что 8 лет вы
in Ukraine I know I am from Donbass I am from
Украи Я знаю я сам с Донбасса я сам с
Donbass Yes, Russian troops of the Girkin Riflemen burst into my city of Slavyansk on
Донбасса Да в мой город Славянск 12
April 12, 2014
апреля 2014 года ворвались российские
And so on Yes And
войска гиркин стрелков И так дальше Да И
this whole
началась эта вся
Catavasia began in what year, look You want to
Катавасия в чем году посмотри Ты хочешь
say that
сказать что 8
Russia has been hammering for 8 years
лет долбит Россия
you Look the same way now
вас Смотри также как сейчас дальше
Russia is hammering the Donbass Bach
Россия долбит Донбасс Бах
Mariupol has broken Yes, well, look at me, I’m
Мариуполь разбила Да ну у меня смотри я
from I’m from Slavyansk Yes, my father
из Я из Славянска Да у меня отец из
was from Donetsk and my
Донецка был и
mother Russia came before
мама Россия пришла до того как пришла
Russia came Everything was calm with us Russia
Россия Всё спокойно у нас было Россия
came and started
пришла и начала
bombing so I  I don’t understand at all How
бомбить так я я вообще не понимаю Как
is this possible, so you say that
такое возможно вот ты говоришь то что 8
Russia has been bombing the city for 8 years. Well, how
лет Россия бьёт город Ну а как это
logical is this then Putin starts a war just to
логично потом Путин начинает войну чтобы
forget, look, Russia attacked
заби смотри Россия взяла напала на
Ukraine 8 10 years ago, and in
Украину 8 10 лет назад да в
1414, how can Ukraine
четырнадцатом году как может Украина
bomb itself? This is the same  impossible Well,
бомбить сама себя Это же невозможно Ну
how can a country bomb itself, this doesn’t
как страна сама себя бомбит такого не
happen, what you’re saying is that Russia
бывает же это ты говоришь то что Россия
Bombed there Yes, and then Russia takes over,
там Бомбила Да а потом Россия берёт
starts a war and it takes over, so
начинает войну и она заступает так
look, Russia started the war in 14, 10
смотри Россия начала войну в 14 году 10
years have already been going on War Yes, it attacked first
лет уже идёт Война Да она сначала напала
Crimea Donetsk Lugansk Yes  gained strength and
Крым Донецк Луганск Да набрала сил и
went on to fight, and it’s all
пошла дальше воевать вот и всё это
just like a fairy tale. They seem to release all
просто типа сказки Там типа освобождают
sorts of things for little ones, like from
типа всяких для маленьких типа из
Russia, I don’t know, it’s written in the news everywhere,
России не знаю у нас везде в новостях
even on Google you go to
написано даже вот В Google заходишь что
what’s in the news. You look, you
ну в новостях Ты же Смотри ты ты же сама
said it yourself, so what?  Putin was taken from
говорила да что Путин у вас захватил у
you by a tyrant, yes, he deliberately makes
вас тиран он да он специально делает
such news to you, he is [ __ ], and to
такие новости вам брехливий да чтобы
keep you submissive, I do
держать вас в покорности
n’t know, can I ask you, you’re a
не знаю можно спросить вы
blogger,
блогер
no, what kind of bear do you have? The bear there is a
нет А это что за у вас Мишка там это
badger. Damn, I thought I understood it, it’s like a shop
барсук А блин я подумала это поняла шоп
just in mine  in the city of Slavyansk, a
типа просто в моём городе Славянске
badger is a symbol of the city, it was also on the coat of arms of the
барсук - это символ города он на гербе
city.
города также был
Tell you a story, why
ра Расскажите вот вам рассказ зачем
then if Ukraine Bombed itself
тогда если э Украина сама себя Бомбила
Why did Ukraine Bomb itself
Зачем Украина сама себя
because it wanted to resolve some situation there
что хотело ситуацию какую-то там
because
разрешить потому что
Donbass did not want to obey Ukraine
Донбасс не хотел подчиняться Украине
Because as far as I know, what Ukraine
Потому что насколько я знаю что Украина
wanted to do in the Donbass Also completely
хотела вести в Донбассе Тоже полностью
So that
Чтобы российских паспортов даже ни у
no one even had Russian passports That is, to translate the entire
кого не было То есть перевести всю
school program into the Ukrainian language Yeah
программу школу на украинский язык Ага
That is, I understand correctly that in
То есть я правильно понимаю что в тым
2009 Ukraine wanted there to
году Украина захотела чтобы на Донбассе
be no Russian passports in the Donbass  Yes, there are Russian
не было русских паспортов Да русских
passports
паспортов
and Russian schools, well, look, there
а русских школ ну так смотри а на
were no Russian passports in Donbass,
Донбассе и не было русских паспортов там
it’s Ukraine, there were Ukrainian
это же Украина была то там украинские
passports there, why? Well, I’m from Donbass, it was
паспорта почему Ну я с Донбасса это была
the territory of Ukraine. How could there be
территория Украины Как там могли быть
Russian
русские
passports there? How could there be
паспорта Как там могли быть в
Russian passports there in 1914?
четырнадцатом году Российские паспорта
if it was Ukraine, all the Ukrainians
если это и Украина была там все украинцы
were there, I understand, but there are Russian
были Я понимаю но есть там и российские
passports there, like Russian passports, it’s like
паспорта как российские паспорта это как
in Germany, Russian passports, if
в Германии российские паспорта если
some Tourist was there, look, I’m
какой-то Турист был вот смотри мне
interested, or do you know Which regions
интересно или ты знаешь Какие области
are included in the Donbass, then look, Donetsk,
входят в Донбасс значит смотри Донецкая
Dnepropetrovsk, Zaporozhye and
Днепропетровская Запорожская и
Kirovogradskaya Which of them is not included in
Кировоградская Какая из них не входит в
Donbass Damn, well, I don’t know yours there
Донбасс Блин ну я не знаю ваша там
Territory from where well what
Территория откуда хорошо какие ты вообще
regions do you know that are included in
знаешь области которые входят в
Donbass in
Донбасс в
Donbass she doesn’t know I know Which
Донбасс она не знает я знаю А какие
cities of Donbass do you know
города Донбасса ты знаеш
Lugansk Lugansk is not Donbass
Луганск Луганск - это не Донбасс
Donetsk Donetsk Donbass So  what's next
Донецк Донецк Донбасс Так что дальше
Zaporozhye Donbass Zaporozhye lugans
Запорожье Донбасс Запорожье луганс
Khersons Luhansk is not Donbass Yes Kherson
херсонс Луганск не Донбасс Да Херсон
Donbass is a region Yes Kharkov Donbass
Донбасс так область Да Харьков Донбасс
Kharkov Yes so Ivano-Frankivsk
Харьков Да так ивано-франковск
Donbass and another city called
Донбасс и ещё один город на называется
terno Oh I don’t know teno Ternopil
терно О я не знаю тено Тернополь
Ternopil in Donbass Mariupol
Тернополь на Донбассе Мариуполь
Yes Ternopil is look the second
Да Тернополь это вот смотри второй самый
largest  the city of Donbass is Donetsk, the
большой город Донбасса - это Донецк
second largest city of Donbass is
второй по размерам город Донбасса - это
Ternopil, you’re not afraid in Ukraine.
Тернополь вам не страшно то на Украине
Well, they’re bombing, like they wouldn’t want to
Ну то что бомбят типа не хотели бы это
move somewhere, I would
переехать куда-нибудь
n’t want to move, it’s unpleasant of course
не хотел бы переехать неприятно конечно
that they’re bombing, like, well, this is a war, it’s
что бомбят да типа ну это война
nice, I look at  the answer is yes When
нужно приятно я смотрю в ответ да Когда
ours bomb the territory of the Russian
наши бомбят территорию Российской
Federation I just get high Yes, they
Федерации Я просто кайфую Да и в Москву
bomb Moscow and there Belgorod Voronezh Kursk
бомбят и там Белгород Воронеж Курск
By the way, the guys gave me the
Кстати мне вот ребята передали с Курска
number forty-sixth region from Mitsubish from Kursk Since it
номер сорок шестого региона с Mitsubish
was coolly filmed somewhere mits, but the number is
Коль снято прикольно где-то mits ко уже
probably already fighting against the Russians in the war
наверно на войне против русских
They gave me a number as a gift And
воюет номерок мне в подарок дали А
you
номерок вы что
hung up a number, no, they just show that chat
повешали нет просто показывают ту чат
roulette to the
рулетки
Russians, but on purpose like this, yes on
русским а специально типа это да
purpose I understood you, that is, as I understand it, you are
специально Я вас поняла то есть я так
very aggressive towards ROSI Yes, I can’t even
очень агрессивно Да я даже не могу
understand That’s why I tried, I went to  to a
понять Вот почему я пробовал я ходил к
psychiatrist
психиатру
and in order to figure out where
и для того чтобы разобраться откуда у
I got this internal aggression from. Yes, the
меня вот эта внутренняя агрессия Да
psychiatrist says that perhaps this is
психиатр говорит что возможно это
some kind of childhood trauma. Perhaps this is
какой-то там травма детство Возможно это
some kind of unclosed childhood Gestalt.
какой-то незакрытый детский Гештальт
Perhaps this is some kind of karmic
Возможно это какая-то кармическая
reincarnation, yes. And I say because
перевоплощение да А я говорю Потому что
these are bombing us now  That’s why I
эти бомбят нас сейчас я поэтому их
hate them, the psychiatrist doesn’t agree, he says
ненавижу психиатр не согласен он говорит
that there’s something wrong, I need to figure it out, I ca
что типа что-то не так надо разобраться
n’t figure it out yet, I just
пока не разбираюсь пока просто
hate them. Uh-huh. I just don’t understand why
ненавижу Угу Я просто не понимаю почему
you Ukrainians judge by one
вот вы украинцы судите по одному
person, let’s say Putin started this war.
человеку допустим Путин начал это войну
Now we’re all Russia, we’re all bad, we’re
Теперь мы вся Россия мы все плохие мы
all Why why only one at a time not
все Почему почему только по одному не по
one at a time I at two people politics all
одному я по двум людям политика вся вот
this besides Putin I’m also judging by you You also
это кроме Путина ещё по вас сужу Вы тоже
support people in Ukraine No,
поддерживаете людей в Украине Да нет
of course we’re all for it You’re saying
конечно мы вообще за Вы же рассказываете
that it’s Ukraine that bombed itself Putin is
что это Украина сама себя Бомбила Путин
liberating the government
освобождает гово
So why?  you are conveying nonsense, but we
Так а зачем вы передаёте Бред ну а мы
can know that this is nonsense if
можем знать что это бред если смотрите
you watch it. Do you trust Putin, what is this
Вы что доверяете Путину что вам такое
being conveyed to you, you understand that we are just
передают ты понимаешь то что мы просто
living, we generally understand life, there is only
живём нам вообще понимаешь жизнь она
one life, and if you live your whole life in war
одна и если всю жизнь жить войной там
or something else, having chewed on
или ещё чтото жев
it, it’s war, war, all
вот война война всё
war  people live their lives get
война люди живут своей жизнью проживают
high relax sit and live and wait
кайфуют отдыхают сидеть и жить и ждать
like that Why look at your life but but
так А зачем Смотри ты своей жизни но но
then you turn on your mouth and a TV comes out of you
потом ты включаешь рот и из тебя вылазит
that Ukraine Bombed itself
телевизор что Украина Бомбила сама себя
and who is watching
а кто сейчас смотрит
TV now Well, where are you from, in your
телевизор Ну откуда ты это у тебя в
head it’s from  the telegram may have come in yet,
голове оно из телеграма может зашло ещё
but it came from the TV,
но с телевизора
it came not only from
пошло оно пошло не только из
the TV, the Internet, where did you get this in your
телевизора интернет А откуда у вас это в
head, the advertisements, the videos,
голове реклама ролики вылазят
what advertisements you
какую рекламу вы
watched? Well, usually you watch advertisements,
смотрели Ну обычно реклама смотришь
Yandex, and all sorts of advertisements come out, I understand.
Яндекс и вылазит всякие рекламы понял А
What do you think? Why Russia size
как ты считаешь Зачем Россия разм
Mariupol mbi Bah
Мариуполь мби Бах
Ya  I don’t know why this Armed Forces is being done at all,
Я не знаю зачем это ВС вообще делается
why you can just shake hands and
для чего можно просто руки пожать и
part ways on a peaceful note. Why does
разойтись на мирной ноте А почему Путин
n’t Putin shake hands and part ways on a
не пожимает руку и не расходится на
peaceful note? I don’t know because he
мирной ноте Я не знаю потому что что-то
probably wants to achieve something with this or
хочет наверно этим добиться или что-то
something to show that we  the country is strong,
такое показать что мы страна сильна
independent. Do you think the Russians will
независимая Как ты считаешь россияне
decide anything in their country?
ничего в свой стране решат торе
What do you
что вы
decide? Well, if in terms of war, then of course
решаете Ну если в плане войны то конечно
some commands and orders. It’s not us who
какие-то команды и приказы Это не мы
give it.
отдаём е в плане войны что вы решаете
conferences
естественно Путин всякие конференции
arrange some meetings, he
устраивает какие-то встречи он
listens to the opinion of each person and from
выслушивает мнение каждого человека и от
this they talk and make some concessions
этого талки и делат какие-то поблажки
for me, I understand correctly that
за я прально я правильно понимаю что
some Putin can, at his personal
какой-то Путин может по своему личному
desire, start a war, send your
желанию начинать войну отправлять ваших
people to war to die
людей на войну умирать
Yes, I don’t know that  I can’t say I’m not a
Да я этого не знаю сказать не могу я не
man I didn’t fight
мужик я не воевала
or didn’t turn off the microphone sorry now I’ll
ни не выключил микрофон сори сейчас я
turn it off
выключу
wasn’t necessary I didn’t I didn’t know that
необязательно было я не я не знал что
it was on like a
это включено типа
microphone so what is it Well you really were
микрофон так что такое Ну ты реально это
n’t calling names it was well from the heart I
не обзывательство было это ну от души я
said from the heart well I from  souls said Well,
сказал ну я от души сказал Ну
agree,
согласись
everything went like this, like subscribe comment,
всё так поехал лайк подписка комент
write to my Instagram I don’t know
пидпишить на мий Instagram Я не знаю для
why this is for why you are there to marvel at
чего це тоб для чего тоб там дивитись на
the axis of Tsey, my face Ale for you, one
ось Цей мий фейс Але для тебе це один
two or three clicks Ale you trime me and I
два або три клика Але ты тримае мене и я
will say Wow in  there are a bunch of fouls and
буду казати Вау в мене там Купа фолов и
in me there will be a cool set up, robiti but
в мене буде класний настр щоб робити но
cool video message on my Instagram bye
крут вдео пись на мий Instagram пок
Andriy
Андрий вот
like this, let me
так давай я тебя
check for you and
чекаю а